The next type is known as Role Culture - that's R-O-L-E,not R-O-double L, by the way,
下一种是著名的角色文化，顺便说一下，是ROLE而不是ROLL，
and this type is usually found in large companies, which have lots of differentlevels in them.
这种类型经常出现在大公司，里面有许多不同的层次。
These organisations usually have separate departments that specialise in things like finance, or sales,or maintenance,or whatever.
这些公司通常有独立的部门，专攻于不同的事情，如金融、销售、维修等等。
Each one is co-ordinated at the top by a small gruop of senior managers, and typically everyone's job is controlled by sets of rules and procedures
每个部门由一小组的高级经理来管理协调，通常每个人的工作受一系列规则和程序的约束，
for example, there are specific job descriptions,rules for discipline,and so on.
例如有一些特定的工作说明，纪律规则等等。
What are the benefits of this kind of culture?
这种文化的优势是什么呢？
Well firstly,because it's found in large organisations,its fixed costs,or overheads as they're known, are low in relation to its output,or what it produces.
首先因为它存在于大型公司，所以固定成本或日常开销相比它的输出或生产要低。
In other words it can achieve economies of scale.
换句话说，它可以实现规模经济。
And secondly,it is particularly successful in business markets where technical expertise is important.
第二，它能在那些专业技术重要的商业市场上取得成功。
On the other hand,this culture is often very slow to recognise the need for change, and even slower to react.
另一方面，这种文化经常认识不到变革的需要，甚至更加难以作出反应。
What kind of person does this type of culture suit?
什么样的人适合这种文化呢？
Well it suits employees who value security,and who don't particularly want to have responsibility.
它适合看重保障、不是很想承担责任的员工。
Moving on now to Task Cultures-this type is found in organisations that are project-oriented.
现在转向任务文化，这种类型存在于以项目为导向的公司里。
You usually find it where the market for the company's product is extremely competitive, or where the products themselves have a short life-span.
你会发现它存在于公司产品极有竞争力的市场上，或寿命很短的产品上。
Usually, top management delegates the projects, the people and other resources.
通常，高层管理人员会委派项目、人员和其他资源。
And once these have been allocated, little day-to-day control is exercised from the top,because this would seem like breaking the rules'.
一旦分配好这些，上层会进行小的日常控制，因为这好像是在打破规则。
Now one of the major benefits of this culture is that it's flexible.
这种文化的主要优势之一是它的灵活性。
But it does have some major disadvantages too.
但是它也有一些重要的不足。
For instance,it can't produce economies of scale or great depth of expertise.
例如，它不能产生规模经济或精深的专业知识。
People who like working in groups or teams refer this type of culture.
喜欢团队工作的人喜欢这种文化。
And finally,the fourth category is called the Person Culture...
最后，第四种类型是个人文化……